Arsenii Ashukha

Moscow, Russia • ⋈ ars.ashuha@gmail.com • ars-ashuha.ru • 23 years old ☺



Summary

I am a second year Master Student at MIPT also I do research at Bayes Group under supervision of prof. Dmitry Vetrov. My research is focused on Bayesian regularization of deep neural nets. At MIPT, MSU, HSE I teach several Machine Learning courses.

Skills: Machine Learning, Deep Learning, Bayesian ML, Python, Hadoop, Hive, Linux, English (B2)

Education

2015 - 2017	Master, Machine Learning, Moscow Institute of Physics and Technology, GPA: 9.0/10.0
Thesis	Regularization of Deep Neural Nets, Supervisor: Prof. D. Vetrov (HSE), A. Dral (MIPT)



2015 - 2016 Irregular Student, Machine Learning, Yandex School of Data Analysis, GPA: 4.8/5.0 Result Six courses were passed and the favorites are Bayesian ML, Deep Learning, Machine Learning



2011 - 2015 Bachelor, Computer Science, Bauman Moscow State Technical University, GPA: 3.7/5.0 Thesis Building of Uncorrelated Kernels for Topic Models, Supervisor: N. Loukachevitch (MSU)



Teaching

- Feb 2016 Feb 2017: Practical Lecturer for Machine Learning course at MIPT (parts 1,2)
- Sep 2016 Now: Lecturer for several classes of Deep Learning courses at MSU and HSE
- Oct 2016 Now: Lecturer for Data Mining in Action course, YouTube records in Russian ©
- Feb 2017 Now: Lecturer for Deep Learning block in Machine Learning course at MIPT
- Feb 2017 Now: Co-head of Scientific Machine Learning seminar for MIPT and HSE Yandex students

Experience

Jun 2016 - Aug 2016

3 month

Yandex, Moscow — Intern at Music Deep Learning Group (E. Krofto)

- Searching similar tracks and building recommendation features using DNN



Dec 2013 - Feb 2016

2 year 1 month p/t

Rambler, Moscow — R&D Engineer at ML Group (A. Gorokhov, P. Klemenkov)

- Improving the quality and performance of user classification using browser history

- Recommendations system for the news posts on rambler.ru

RAMBLER&Co

Jun 2013 - Aug 2013

3 month

Rambler, Moscow — Intern at Search Group (M. Karpenko)

- Users query classification to show a mixing in search results

RAMBLER&Co

Publications

Dmitry Molchanov, Arseniy Ashuha and Dmitry Vetrov

- 1. Dropout-based Automatic Relevance Determination Bayesian Deep Learning Workshop, Neural Information Processing Systems 2016
 - Arseniy Ashuha and Natalia Loukachevitch
- 2. Bigram Anchor Words Topic Model
 International Conference on Image Analysis, Social Networks and Texts 2016